{"items": [{"question": "2. Are egocentric people easy to get along with?", "answer": "1. Is rejection usually a blow to one\u2019s ego?", "options": ["5. Is altruism a characteristic of selfish people?", "3. Does an egomaniac have a normal personality?", "1. Is rejection usually a blow to one\u2019s ego?", "7. Is an alternate plan necessarily inferior?"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "4. Are egomaniacal tendencies a sign of maturity?", "answer": "3. Does an egomaniac have a normal personality?", "options": ["5. Is altruism a characteristic of selfish people?", "3. Does an egomaniac have a normal personality?", "7. Is an alternate plan necessarily inferior?", "9. Does alteration imply keeping things the same?"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "6. Are altruistic tendencies common to egoists?", "answer": "5. Is altruism a characteristic of selfish people?", "options": ["5. Is altruism a characteristic of selfish people?", "7. Is an alternate plan necessarily inferior?", "9. Does alteration imply keeping things the same?", "11. Is your alter ego usually quite similar to yourself?"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "8. Does an alternative allow you some freedom of choice?", "answer": "7. Is an alternate plan necessarily inferior?", "options": ["9. Does alteration imply keeping things the same?", "7. Is an alternate plan necessarily inferior?", "11. Is your alter ego usually quite similar to yourself?", ""], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "10. Do excitable people often engage in altercations?", "answer": "9. Does alteration imply keeping things the same?", "options": ["", "11. Is your alter ego usually quite similar to yourself?", "2. Is modesty one of the characteristics of the egotist?", "9. Does alteration imply keeping things the same?"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013no, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013no, 5\u2013no, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013no, 8\u2013yes, 9\u2013no, 10\u2013yes, 11\u2013yes", "answer": "11. Is your alter ego usually quite similar to yourself?", "options": ["", "4. Does an introvert pay much attention to himself?", "11. Is your alter ego usually quite similar to yourself?", "2. Is modesty one of the characteristics of the egotist?"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Do you understand the words?  1. Is an internist an expert in diagnosis?YESNO  2. Is a gynecologist familiar with the female reproductive organs?YESNO  3. Does an obstetrician specialize in diseases of childhood?YESNO  4. Does a pediatrician deliver babies?YESNO  5. If you had a skin disease, would you visit a dermatologist?YESNO  6. If you had trouble with your vision would you visit an orthopedist?YESNO  7. Is an ophthalmologist an eye specialist?YESNO  8. Does a cardiologist treat bone fractures?YESNO  9. Is a neurologist a nerve specialist?YESNO10. If you were nervous, tense, overly anxious, constantly fearful for noapparent reasons, would a psychiatrist be the specialist to see?YESNO", "answer": "", "options": ["2. Is modesty one of the characteristics of the egotist?", "4. Does an introvert pay much attention to himself?", "6. Are most normal people ambiverts?", ""], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "3. Is an altruist selfish?", "answer": "2. Is modesty one of the characteristics of the egotist?", "options": ["4. Does an introvert pay much attention to himself?", "2. Is modesty one of the characteristics of the egotist?", "8. Does a misogynist enjoy the company of women?", "6. Are most normal people ambiverts?"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "5. Does an extrovert prefer solitude to companionship?", "answer": "4. Does an introvert pay much attention to himself?", "options": ["8. Does a misogynist enjoy the company of women?", "6. Are most normal people ambiverts?", "4. Does an introvert pay much attention to himself?", "10. Does a misogamist try to avoid marriage?"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "7. Does a misanthrope like people?", "answer": "6. Are most normal people ambiverts?", "options": ["6. Are most normal people ambiverts?", "10. Does a misogamist try to avoid marriage?", "8. Does a misogynist enjoy the company of women?", ""], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "9. Does an ascetic lead a life of luxury?", "answer": "8. Does a misogynist enjoy the company of women?", "options": ["10. Does a misogamist try to avoid marriage?", "13. Does a misogynist enjoy female companionship?YESNO14. Are unmarried people necessarily misogamous?YESNO15. Are bachelors necessarily misogynous?YESNO16. Is asceticism compatible with luxurious living and the pursuit ofpleasure?YESNO17. Does a polyandrist have more than one husband?YESNO", "", "8. Does a misogynist enjoy the company of women?"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013no, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013yes, 5\u2013no, 6\u2013yes, 7\u2013 no, 8\u2013no, 9\u2013no, 10\u2013yes", "answer": "10. Does a misogamist try to avoid marriage?", "options": ["", "", "10. Does a misogamist try to avoid marriage?", "13. Does a misogynist enjoy female companionship?YESNO14. Are unmarried people necessarily misogamous?YESNO15. Are bachelors necessarily misogynous?YESNO16. Is asceticism compatible with luxurious living and the pursuit ofpleasure?YESNO17. Does a polyandrist have more than one husband?YESNO"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Do you understand the words?  1. Is an internist an expert in diagnosis?YESNO  2. Is a gynecologist familiar with the female reproductive organs?YESNO  3. Does an obstetrician specialize in diseases of childhood?YESNO  4. Does a pediatrician deliver babies?YESNO  5. If you had a skin disease, would you visit a dermatologist?YESNO  6. If you had trouble with your vision would you visit an orthopedist?YESNO  7. Is an ophthalmologist an eye specialist?YESNO  8. Does a cardiologist treat bone fractures?YESNO  9. Is a neurologist a nerve specialist?YESNO10. If you were nervous, tense, overly anxious, constantly fearful for noapparent reasons, would a psychiatrist be the specialist to see?YESNO", "answer": "", "options": ["", "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013no, 5\u2013yes, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013yes, 8\u2013no, 9\u2013yes, 10\u2013yes", "", "13. Does a misogynist enjoy female companionship?YESNO14. Are unmarried people necessarily misogamous?YESNO15. Are bachelors necessarily misogynous?YESNO16. Is asceticism compatible with luxurious living and the pursuit ofpleasure?YESNO17. Does a polyandrist have more than one husband?YESNO"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013yes, 4\u2013no, 5\u2013yes, 6\u2013yes, 7\u2013no, 8\u2013yes, 9\u2013no,10\u2013yes, 11\u2013yes, 12\u2013no, 13\u2013no, 14\u2013no, 15\u2013no, 16\u2013no, 17\u2013yes", "answer": "13. Does a misogynist enjoy female companionship?YESNO14. Are unmarried people necessarily misogamous?YESNO15. Are bachelors necessarily misogynous?YESNO16. Is asceticism compatible with luxurious living and the pursuit ofpleasure?YESNO17. Does a polyandrist have more than one husband?YESNO", "options": ["KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013no, 5\u2013yes, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013yes, 8\u2013no, 9\u2013yes, 10\u2013yes", "", "Does a treatise on obstetrics deal with childbirth?YESNO  2. Does gynecology deal with the female reproductive organs?YESNO  3. Is pediatrics concerned with the diseases of old age?YESNO  4. Does pedagogy refer to teaching?YESNO  5. Is a pedagogue an expert teacher?YESNO  6. Is a demagogue interested in the welfare of the people?YESNO  7. Is a lion a pachyderm?YESNO  8. Is the epidermis one of the layers of the skin?YESNO  9. Is dermatitis an inflammation of one of the limbs?YESNO10. Is a taxidermist a medical practitioner?YESNO11. Is an ophthalmologist a medical doctor?YESNO12. Is an optometrist a medical doctor?YESNO13. Does an optician prescribe glasses?", "13. Does a misogynist enjoy female companionship?YESNO14. Are unmarried people necessarily misogamous?YESNO15. Are bachelors necessarily misogynous?YESNO16. Is asceticism compatible with luxurious living and the pursuit ofpleasure?YESNO17. Does a polyandrist have more than one husband?YESNO"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Do you understand the words?  1. Is an internist an expert in diagnosis?YESNO  2. Is a gynecologist familiar with the female reproductive organs?YESNO  3. Does an obstetrician specialize in diseases of childhood?YESNO  4. Does a pediatrician deliver babies?YESNO  5. If you had a skin disease, would you visit a dermatologist?YESNO  6. If you had trouble with your vision would you visit an orthopedist?YESNO  7. Is an ophthalmologist an eye specialist?YESNO  8. Does a cardiologist treat bone fractures?YESNO  9. Is a neurologist a nerve specialist?YESNO10. If you were nervous, tense, overly anxious, constantly fearful for noapparent reasons, would a psychiatrist be the specialist to see?YESNO", "answer": "", "options": ["Does a treatise on obstetrics deal with childbirth?YESNO  2. Does gynecology deal with the female reproductive organs?YESNO  3. Is pediatrics concerned with the diseases of old age?YESNO  4. Does pedagogy refer to teaching?YESNO  5. Is a pedagogue an expert teacher?YESNO  6. Is a demagogue interested in the welfare of the people?YESNO  7. Is a lion a pachyderm?YESNO  8. Is the epidermis one of the layers of the skin?YESNO  9. Is dermatitis an inflammation of one of the limbs?YESNO10. Is a taxidermist a medical practitioner?YESNO11. Is an ophthalmologist a medical doctor?YESNO12. Is an optometrist a medical doctor?YESNO13. Does an optician prescribe glasses?", "", "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013no, 5\u2013yes, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013yes, 8\u2013no, 9\u2013yes, 10\u2013yes", "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013yes, 5\u2013no, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013no, 8\u2013yes, 9\u2013no, 10\u2013no, 11\u2013yes, 12\u2013no, 13\u2013no"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "", "answer": "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013no, 5\u2013yes, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013yes, 8\u2013no, 9\u2013yes, 10\u2013yes", "options": ["KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013yes, 5\u2013no, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013no, 8\u2013yes, 9\u2013no, 10\u2013no, 11\u2013yes, 12\u2013no, 13\u2013no", "A gynecologist\u2019s patients are mostly men.TRUEFALSE  2. Ophthalmology is the study of eye diseases.TRUEFALSE  3. Orthopedics is the specialty dealing with the bones and joints.TRUEFALSE4. A cardiac patient has a heart ailment.TRUEFALSE  5. A person with a bad \u201cbite\u201d may profit from orthodontia.TRUEFALSE  6. Neuralgia is a disease of the bones.TRUEFALSE  7. A neurosis is the same as a psychosis.TRUEFALSE  8. Neuritis is inflammation of the nerves.TRUEFALSE  9. Psychiatry is a medical specialty that deals with mental, emotional,and personality disturbances.TRUEFALSE10. A cardiograph is a device for recording heartbeats.TRUEFALSEPsychiatric treatment is designed to relieve tensions, fears, andinsecurities.TRUEFALSE12. A doctor who specializes in pediatrics has very old patients.", "Does a treatise on obstetrics deal with childbirth?YESNO  2. Does gynecology deal with the female reproductive organs?YESNO  3. Is pediatrics concerned with the diseases of old age?YESNO  4. Does pedagogy refer to teaching?YESNO  5. Is a pedagogue an expert teacher?YESNO  6. Is a demagogue interested in the welfare of the people?YESNO  7. Is a lion a pachyderm?YESNO  8. Is the epidermis one of the layers of the skin?YESNO  9. Is dermatitis an inflammation of one of the limbs?YESNO10. Is a taxidermist a medical practitioner?YESNO11. Is an ophthalmologist a medical doctor?YESNO12. Is an optometrist a medical doctor?YESNO13. Does an optician prescribe glasses?", "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013no, 5\u2013yes, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013yes, 8\u2013no, 9\u2013yes, 10\u2013yes"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "YESNO", "answer": "Does a treatise on obstetrics deal with childbirth?YESNO  2. Does gynecology deal with the female reproductive organs?YESNO  3. Is pediatrics concerned with the diseases of old age?YESNO  4. Does pedagogy refer to teaching?YESNO  5. Is a pedagogue an expert teacher?YESNO  6. Is a demagogue interested in the welfare of the people?YESNO  7. Is a lion a pachyderm?YESNO  8. Is the epidermis one of the layers of the skin?YESNO  9. Is dermatitis an inflammation of one of the limbs?YESNO10. Is a taxidermist a medical practitioner?YESNO11. Is an ophthalmologist a medical doctor?YESNO12. Is an optometrist a medical doctor?YESNO13. Does an optician prescribe glasses?", "options": ["A gynecologist\u2019s patients are mostly men.TRUEFALSE  2. Ophthalmology is the study of eye diseases.TRUEFALSE  3. Orthopedics is the specialty dealing with the bones and joints.TRUEFALSE4. A cardiac patient has a heart ailment.TRUEFALSE  5. A person with a bad \u201cbite\u201d may profit from orthodontia.TRUEFALSE  6. Neuralgia is a disease of the bones.TRUEFALSE  7. A neurosis is the same as a psychosis.TRUEFALSE  8. Neuritis is inflammation of the nerves.TRUEFALSE  9. Psychiatry is a medical specialty that deals with mental, emotional,and personality disturbances.TRUEFALSE10. A cardiograph is a device for recording heartbeats.TRUEFALSEPsychiatric treatment is designed to relieve tensions, fears, andinsecurities.TRUEFALSE12. A doctor who specializes in pediatrics has very old patients.", "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013yes, 5\u2013no, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013no, 8\u2013yes, 9\u2013no, 10\u2013no, 11\u2013yes, 12\u2013no, 13\u2013no", "1. Is rejection usually a blow to one\u2019s ego?", "Does a treatise on obstetrics deal with childbirth?YESNO  2. Does gynecology deal with the female reproductive organs?YESNO  3. Is pediatrics concerned with the diseases of old age?YESNO  4. Does pedagogy refer to teaching?YESNO  5. Is a pedagogue an expert teacher?YESNO  6. Is a demagogue interested in the welfare of the people?YESNO  7. Is a lion a pachyderm?YESNO  8. Is the epidermis one of the layers of the skin?YESNO  9. Is dermatitis an inflammation of one of the limbs?YESNO10. Is a taxidermist a medical practitioner?YESNO11. Is an ophthalmologist a medical doctor?YESNO12. Is an optometrist a medical doctor?YESNO13. Does an optician prescribe glasses?"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "", "answer": "KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013yes, 5\u2013no, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013no, 8\u2013yes, 9\u2013no, 10\u2013no, 11\u2013yes, 12\u2013no, 13\u2013no", "options": ["KEY:  1\u2013yes, 2\u2013yes, 3\u2013no, 4\u2013yes, 5\u2013no, 6\u2013no, 7\u2013no, 8\u2013yes, 9\u2013no, 10\u2013no, 11\u2013yes, 12\u2013no, 13\u2013no", "1. Is rejection usually a blow to one\u2019s ego?", "3. Does an egomaniac have a normal personality?", "A gynecologist\u2019s patients are mostly men.TRUEFALSE  2. Ophthalmology is the study of eye diseases.TRUEFALSE  3. Orthopedics is the specialty dealing with the bones and joints.TRUEFALSE4. A cardiac patient has a heart ailment.TRUEFALSE  5. A person with a bad \u201cbite\u201d may profit from orthodontia.TRUEFALSE  6. Neuralgia is a disease of the bones.TRUEFALSE  7. A neurosis is the same as a psychosis.TRUEFALSE  8. Neuritis is inflammation of the nerves.TRUEFALSE  9. Psychiatry is a medical specialty that deals with mental, emotional,and personality disturbances.TRUEFALSE10. A cardiograph is a device for recording heartbeats.TRUEFALSEPsychiatric treatment is designed to relieve tensions, fears, andinsecurities.TRUEFALSE12. A doctor who specializes in pediatrics has very old patients."], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "TRUEFALSE13. A geriatrician has very young patients.TRUEFALSE", "answer": "A gynecologist\u2019s patients are mostly men.TRUEFALSE  2. Ophthalmology is the study of eye diseases.TRUEFALSE  3. Orthopedics is the specialty dealing with the bones and joints.TRUEFALSE4. A cardiac patient has a heart ailment.TRUEFALSE  5. A person with a bad \u201cbite\u201d may profit from orthodontia.TRUEFALSE  6. Neuralgia is a disease of the bones.TRUEFALSE  7. A neurosis is the same as a psychosis.TRUEFALSE  8. Neuritis is inflammation of the nerves.TRUEFALSE  9. Psychiatry is a medical specialty that deals with mental, emotional,and personality disturbances.TRUEFALSE10. A cardiograph is a device for recording heartbeats.TRUEFALSEPsychiatric treatment is designed to relieve tensions, fears, andinsecurities.TRUEFALSE12. A doctor who specializes in pediatrics has very old patients.", "options": ["5. Is altruism a characteristic of selfish people?", "1. Is rejection usually a blow to one\u2019s ego?", "3. Does an egomaniac have a normal personality?", "A gynecologist\u2019s patients are mostly men.TRUEFALSE  2. Ophthalmology is the study of eye diseases.TRUEFALSE  3. Orthopedics is the specialty dealing with the bones and joints.TRUEFALSE4. A cardiac patient has a heart ailment.TRUEFALSE  5. A person with a bad \u201cbite\u201d may profit from orthodontia.TRUEFALSE  6. Neuralgia is a disease of the bones.TRUEFALSE  7. A neurosis is the same as a psychosis.TRUEFALSE  8. Neuritis is inflammation of the nerves.TRUEFALSE  9. Psychiatry is a medical specialty that deals with mental, emotional,and personality disturbances.TRUEFALSE10. A cardiograph is a device for recording heartbeats.TRUEFALSEPsychiatric treatment is designed to relieve tensions, fears, andinsecurities.TRUEFALSE12. A doctor who specializes in pediatrics has very old patients."], "answer_index": 4}], "title": "session_one_yes_no", "total": 19}